Guide to the Lindseth Collection of Alice Ephemera MSS.368
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Series VIII: Art
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 23/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 23)
    Description: Inkstand: Avoid Hot drinks; otherwise, you will be troubled with debility or weakness, loss of appetite, indigestion and many other diseases arising from a deranged condition of the stomach.
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 24/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 24)
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 25/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 25)
  - Alice Among the Fortune Tellers 26/26, [Undated] (Box 38, Item 26)
  - Malice in Wonderland -- Julie Inman, 1980 (Flat-file-folder [large folder])